<event name="CO_SIGILMASTER_FIRSTMEET">
	<text>Upon arrival at the beacon, you don't immediately understand what's going on, because the place is shrouded in clouds of stardust - your sensors haven't detected a nebula in this part of space.
While you're messing with the sensors, trying to figure out what's wrong with them, you are not immediately hailed... However, not a single sound was heard on the transmission.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Wait until you hear something.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You decided to wait. To your suprise, it didn't last as long as you expected, after a minute of silence, a slightly hoarse but remarkably confident voice was heard, certain of what it was saying.
"... Someone asked me to name two structures that hold water. I was like... Well damn.
Laugh."

You feel like you took a wrong turn when you decided to wait.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Respond with an equally stupid pun. Maybe, that's what they want from you.</text>
				<event>
					<text>You tried to make a bad joke. And you succeeded, it really was bad. At least that's what you conclude from the fact that the person who contacted you didn't make a sound after your stand-up. Maybe you should have just kept quiet.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Keep quiet and start charging the FTL drive before you get an answer.</text>
						<event></event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>>Keep quiet and wait until you hear something.</text>
						<event></event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Try to make a good joke this time.</text>
						<event></event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Cut the feed before it's too late. You already know you can't stand this for too long.</text>
				<event>
					<text>"...Now let's get serious. Not so fast, Renegade. You've already noticed your sensors are malfunctioning a bit, haven't you? Before you even try to move on, I think it's best for you to know that this nebulous zone is booby-trapped.
And outside of it, you are already expected. If you don't want to get to your final destination, you can cut off the transmission and try to leave now. Otherwise, we'll make a deal...
I have plenty of time, I can wait for your decision. YOU don't have much of it. You're what they call a man on a mission."</text>
					<choice>
						<text>""</text>
						<event></event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>.</text>
						<event></event>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>"Go on, what do you want?"</text>
						<event></event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Cut the feed before you even hear something. There are some more important things to do.</text>
		<event>
			<text>"...Are you in a hurry, huh? It can wait, don't worry. You Renegades are interesting guys. Just like us... I don't even always distinguish yours from ours. However, there is a significant gap between us."</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>"Who are we're talking to? What are you talking about?"</text>
				<event>
					<text>"You justify your dirty crimes with a "sacred mission", "privileges of the defender of the Best Interests", "lack of better options".
Even with the understanding that everyone has different standards, it is impossible to look at your "feats" without gagging. You are the same scumbags as us, only worse. You are pirates.
Not understanding what you are doing and why. And for some reason, with your "mission", this idiotic cover, you get away with everything. Haven't you thought about it?"</text>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>"Shut it. If it means sacrificing the people of the Rebel fleet, some pitiful pirates, or even just civilians to save the Federation, we won't hesitate. You're just our another nuisance."</text>
						<event>
							<text>"Bold of you to conclude so, Renegade. I mean naive, but you do you. There's nothing left we can talk about now. Later we'll meet again, but now I just..."
Without finishing his speech, the stranger from the nebula cuts off the transmission. Deciding not to waste any more time thinking about what happened, you return to the malfunctioning sensors.
A detailed diagnostic shows that there are no problems. Apparently, your sensors were hacked remotely.</text>
							<choice hidden="true">
								<text>Continue.</text>
								<event>
									<text>.</text>
								</event>
							</choice>
						</event>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>"Whoever you are, you better not get into trouble. If you know who we are, you know whose power we have."</text>
				<event>
					<text>"Trouble you say. Firstly, you Renegades are naive... Naive and stupid. Like everyone else before you, you won't remember this, but still...
Anything that's none of your business is not your problem. Don't create problems. You won't get away with it."</text>
					<choice>
						<text>.</text>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>.</text>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>



<ship name="CO_ANGEL_BATTLESHIP_PURE" auto_blueprint="CO_ANGEL_BATTLESHIP_PURE">
	<destroyed load="CO_RAVAGER_GENERIC_DEFEAT"/>
</ship>
<event name="CO_SIGILMASTER_LOAD">
	<text>There's a Capra Angel ship.</text>
	<ship load="CO_ANGEL_BATTLESHIP_PURE" hostile="false"/>
	<choice>
		<text>Hello.</text>
		<event>
			<text>...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice>
		<text>Beat the crap out of it.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Let it go.</text>
			<ship hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>